Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
1937-1992, undated
1936 1992
North Carolina State University Athletics
UA 015.401
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audio/Visual Materials collection contains primarily moving image recordings of North Carolina State University varsity football games. These recordings were captured by the Department of Athletics for coaching and review purposes, and are mostly without sound, commentary, or other narration. Also included in this collection are a small number of narrated moving image recordings on the topics of NC State football and collegiate football in general, intended for airing over television stations; as well as miscellaneous footage of individual players and coaches at NC State. Materials range in date from 1937 to 1992, and some recordings are undated.
In 1892, the first official football game at NC State was played against a local prep school, Raleigh Male Academy; in 1893, State played their first intercollegiate game against Tennessee. The 1895 team was the first to wear the now traditional red and white colored uniforms, a change from their original pink and blue uniforms. The first on-campus football game was played in 1907 on the field that would later become Riddick Stadium. In 1918, John Ripple becomes the first athlete at NC State to be named an All-American in any sport, and in 1978, Ted Brown becomes the first African American to be named an All-American in football. The football team adopted the nickname “Wolfpack” in 1921, although all other sports continued to use the name “Red Terrors.” In 1930, the first night game was played at Riddick Stadium, and ended in a 37-0 victory against High Point. The team was invited to their first post-season bowl game in 1947, the January 1 Gator bowl against the University of Oklahoma. On October 21 1950, the football team played their first televised game against Maryland. The new Carter Stadium (renamed Carter-Finley Stadium in 1979) opened on October 8, 1966, and in 1967, Marcus Martin became the first African American member of the football team. In 1967, the team won their first bowl game (the Liberty Bowl) against Georgia with a score of 14-7. The team won their first ACC championship in 1979.
173.25 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
USE COPIES OF ALL RECORDINGS MUST BE PRODUCED PRIOR TO PATRON VIEWING.
Transferred from North Carolina State University, Athletics.
USE COPIES OF ALL RECORDINGS MUST BE PRODUCED PRIOR TO PATRON VIEWING.
Recordings are arranged chronologically by season, and alphabetically within each season by opponent. Some seasons have general footage (not from a specific game or opponent); these recordings can be found listed after all of the game footage from that season. Recordings that could not be identified by date or opponent are found at the end of the list and labeled as "miscellaneous football footage."
1892 The first official football game at the North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts is played against a local prep school, Raleigh Male Academy.
1893 The North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts play their first intercollegiate game against Tennessee.
1895 The now traditional red and white colored uniforms are adopted, a change from the school's original pink and blue uniforms.
1907 The first on-campus football game is played on the field that would later become Riddick Stadium
1918 John Ripple becomes the first athlete at North Carolina State College to be named an All-American in any sport.
1921 The football team adopts the nickname “Wolfpack”.
1930 The first night game is played at Riddick Stadium, ending in a 37-0 victory against High Point.
1947 The football team play in their first post-season bowl game, the Gator Bowl, against the University of Oklahoma.
October 21, 1950 The football team play in their first televised game, against the University of Maryland.
October 8, 1966 Carter Stadium opens.
1967 Marcus Martin becomes the first African-American member of the football team.
1967 The football team wins their first bowl game (the Liberty Bowl) against Georgia, by a score of 14-7.
1978 Ted Brown becomes the first African-American to be named an All-American in football at North Carolina State University.
1979 Carter Stadium is renamed Carter-Finley Stadium.
1979 The football team wins their first Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) championship.
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audio/Visual Materials collection contains primarily moving image recordings of North Carolina State University varsity football games. These recordings were captured by the Department of Athletics for coaching and review purposes, and are mostly without sound, commentary, or other narration. Also included in this collection are a small number of narrated moving image recordings on the topics of NC State football and collegiate football in general, intended for airing over television stations; as well as miscellaneous footage of individual players and coaches at NC State. Materials range in date from 1937 to 1992, and some recordings are undated.
North Carolina State University Athletics; North Carolina State College Athletics; North Carolina State College--History; North Carolina State University Athletics; North Carolina State Wolfpack Football team; North Carolina State University--History; North Carolina State University--Sports--History; North Carolina College athletes; North Carolina History Football
- Roman Gabriel passing (1960-1961), Atlantic Coast Conference highlights (1972), Liberty Bowl (1963), 1960-1972 (Carton 1)
  MII cassette; Approximate runtime: unknown; black white and color, no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 1938 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes 30 seconds; black white, no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 1939 (Carton 1)
  VHS cassette; Approximate runtime: unknown; black white, sound (background music, not game-descriptive commentary)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 1938 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Miami, 1957 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 15 minutes; black white; no sound
- Roman Gabriel passing (vs. UCLA and Maryland), 1959 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes; black white, no sound
- Roman Gabriel passing, 1960-1961 (Carton 1)
- SC - Highlights (1 of 2), 1961 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 12 minutes; black white, no sound
- SC - Highlights (2 of 2), 1961 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 11 minutes; black white, no sound
- Index of clips in "Highlights" films, 1961 (Carton 1, Folder 1)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as #1 of 2], 1966 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 10 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as #2 of 2], 1966 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 10 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as JV Reel #3], 1966 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as Frosh #3 of 3/Secondary Mistakes], 1966 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (#1), 1975 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (#2), 1975 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (#3), 1975 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (#4), 1975 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Oregon State (#2), 1976 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. Oregon State (#3), 1976 (Carton 1)
- Long runs - passes, 1978 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. WM Mary (#3), 1967 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 18 minutes, 20 seconds; black and white; no sound
- Player clips - Bill Hensley (2 min.), 1959 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 2 minutes; black white, no sound
- Field goal, 1957 (Carton 1)
  MII cassette; Approximate runtime: unknown; black and white; no sound
  - UNC vs. State, 1939 (Carton 112)
    This film is damaged and cannot be playes without extensive conservation work.
- All-American Football Team, 1961 (Carton 1)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 22 minutes; black white, sound
- ACC Highlights, 1975 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs.Clemson, 1945 (Reel 22)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 3 Oct. 1959 (Reel 21)
- Roman Gabriel footage, 1950s-1960s (Carton 91)
- Liberty Bowl, 1963 (Carton 91)
- Liberty Bowl, 1963 (Reel 23)
- NC State vs. Mississippi (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as Reel I], 1964 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Mississippi (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as Reel IV], 1964 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as #2 of 2], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Duke, 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Florida (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
  This film has been reproduced in the following formats: digital beta cassette [stored in carton 8], .mp4 video file
- NC State vs. Florida (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2 of 2 Offense], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Georgia, 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 10 minutes, 30 seconds; color; sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as #1 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as #2 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 8 minutes; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as #3 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Michigan State (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as #2 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 11 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Michigan State (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as #3 of 3], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Mississippi State (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as Reel II], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes; color; sound
- NC State vs. Mississippi State (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as Reel III], 1966 (Carton 2)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 10 minutes; color; sound
- NC State vs. Southern Mississippi, 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 3) [labeled on cansiter as Offense #1 of 2], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 3) [labeled on container as Defense #2 of 2], 1966 (Carton 2)
- NC State vs. Georgia - Liberty Bowl (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 111)
  These files were originally received on a DVD. The DVD is not available for patron use. Copies of files from this DVD are available upon request.
  DVD; Approximate runtime: 33 minutes; color; silent
- NC State vs. Georgia - Liberty Bowl (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 111)
- 1967 Liberty Bowl (color/silent) (Box 111)
  Betacam
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as Frosh #1 of 3], 1967 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as Frosh #2 of 3], 1967 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as Frosh #3 of 3], 1967 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 6 minutes; black white; sound
- Tape (miscellaneous football footage) (on cassette with 1988 Highlights, 1990 Recruiting), 1967 (Carton 59)
  MII cassette; Approximate runtime: 90 minutes; color; sound
- Inventory of footage on 1967 Tape, 1988 Highlights, 1990 Recruiting, 1967-1990 (Carton 59, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Coast Conference highlights (1 of 3), 1967 (Reel 11)
- Atlantic Coast Conference highlights (2 of 3), 1967 (Reel 14)
- Atlantic Coast Conference highlights (3 of 3), 1967 (Reel 15)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense, 1 of 2], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense, 2 of 2], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense, 1 of 2], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 8) [labled on canister as Defense, 2 of 2], 2 Nov. 1968 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Clemson (highlights), 1968 (Reel 24)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 8 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Florida State (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Florida State (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Florida State (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 6 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Florida State (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 12 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #1], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as Offense #2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #1], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as Defense #2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 4], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Oklahoma (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1968 (Carton 4)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 10 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist Univeristy (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Southern Methodist University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1969 (Carton 5)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 4 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State Frosh vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Frosh (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as #2 of 3], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State Frosh vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Frosh (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as #3 of 3], 1968 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as #1 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as #2 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as #3 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as #4 of 4], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 1968 (Carton 5)
- Red/White game, 23 Mar. 1968 (Carton 4)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 3 minutes; black white; sound
- Highlights, 1968 (Reel 25)
- Highlights ("A Championship Year"), 1968 (Carton 5)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 22 minutes; color; sound
- Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) football highlights (1 of 3), 1968 (Reel 8)
- Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) football highlights (2 of 3), 1968 (Reel 9)
- Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) football highlights (3 of 3), 1968 (Reel 10)
- NC State vs. Maryland [labeled on canister as Defense], 27 Sept. 1969 [possibly 1970] (Carton 7)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 7 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 3) [labeled on box as coaches' huddle, TV cameras and crowd, cheerleaders and sideline], 1969 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 3) [labeled on box as crowd, warm-up sidelines, cheerleaders at night), 1969 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 3) [labeled on box as band, ABC action], 1969 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 4 minutes; color; no sound
- Red/White game (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as Red Offense first half], 1969 (Carton 5)
- Red/White game (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as White Offense first half], 1969 (Carton 5)
- Red/White game (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as Red Offense second half], 1969 (Carton 5)
- Red/White game (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as White Offense second half], 1969 (Carton 5)
- Player clips, 1969 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 30 seconds; color; sound
- Index of clips in "Player Clips" film, 1969 (Carton 6, Folder 1)
- Punts, 1969 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 13 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 5) [labeled on canister as Offense #1 of 2], 17 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 5) [labeled on canister as Offense #2 of 2], 17 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 5) [labeled on canister as Defense #1 of 2], 17 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 5) [labeled on canister as Defense #2 of 2], 17 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke Frosh Reel No. 3 of 4, 23 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 8 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense, 1 of 2], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense, 2 of 2], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Defense 1 of 2], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2], 10 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense, 1 of 2], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Florida (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 9 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Florida (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as Offense, 2 of 2], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Florida (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Florida (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Kentucky (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 6)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 8 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Kentucky (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Kentucky (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Kentucky (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Kentucky (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense 1 of 2], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Kentucky (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense 2 of 2], 31 Oct. 1970 (Carton 7)